{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Advanced Database Systems",
    "Term": "Midterms",
    "Title": "Data Analytics",
    "LastModified": "21 October 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "04_Handout_1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "It is a database designed to enable and support business intelligence activities, especially analytics.",
      "answer": "date warehouse",
      "choices": [
        "date warehouse",
        "data storage location",
        "data plant",
        "data interactions"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about data warehouse?",
      "answer": "always implemented on the relational database management system (RDBMS) technology like SQL",
      "choices": [
        "intended to perform queries and analysis",
        "optimized for data retrieval, not for transaction processing",
        "centralizes and consolidates large amounts of data from multiple sources",
        "always implemented on the relational database management system (RDBMS) technology like SQL"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about data warehouse?",
      "answer": "allow users to analyze the data using elaborate and complex multi-dimensional views",
      "choices": [
        "allows organizations to derive valuable business insights from their data to improve decision-making",
        "can be considered an organizationâ€™s 'single source of truth'",
        "intended to perform queries and analysis",
        "allow users to analyze the data using elaborate and complex multi-dimensional views"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "The DW can analyze data about a particular subject or functional area.",
      "answer": "subject-oriented",
      "choices": [
        "subject-oriented",
        "integrated",
        "time-variant",
        "non-volatile"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about subject-oriented?",
      "answer": "Once data is in a data warehouse, it is stable and does not change.",
      "choices": [
        "Subjects can be products, customers, departments, regions, etc",
        "The functional area can be sales, marketing, finance, distribution, etc",
        "Focuses on the data rather than on the processes that modify the data",
        "Once data is in a data warehouse, it is stable and does not change."
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "The DW creates consistency among different data types from different sources.",
      "answer": "integrated",
      "choices": [
        "subject-oriented",
        "integrated",
        "time-variant",
        "non-volatile"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about integrated?",
      "answer": "Data in a Data Warehouse (DW) reflects the flow of information over time and can be organized by weeks, months, or years",
      "choices": [
        "DW must conform to a common format that is acceptable throughout the organization",
        "The DW creates consistency among different data types from different sources",
        "A student's level in the database can be categorized as 'freshman', 'sophomore', 'junior', or 'senior' in the accounting department, and as 'FR', 'SO', 'JR', or 'SR' in the computer information systems department.",
        "Data in a Data Warehouse (DW) reflects the flow of information over time and can be organized by weeks, months, or years"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Data in a Data Warehouse (DW) reflects the flow of information over time and can be organized by weeks, months, or years.",
      "answer": "time-variant",
      "choices": [
        "subject-oriented",
        "integrated",
        "time-variant",
        "non-volatile"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which best exemplifies time-variant?",
      "answer": "When data for previous weekly sales is uploaded to the data warehouse, it also updates time-dependent subjects such as weekly, monthly, and yearly data for products, customers, stores, and more.",
      "choices": [
        "When data for previous weekly sales is uploaded to the data warehouse, it also updates time-dependent subjects such as weekly, monthly, and yearly data for products, customers, stores, and more.",
        "A student's level in the database can be categorized as 'freshman', 'sophomore', 'junior', or 'senior' in the accounting department, and as 'FR', 'SO', 'JR', or 'SR' in the computer information systems department.",
        "Subjects can be products, customers, departments, regions, etc",
        "Focuses on the data rather than on the processes that modify the data"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Once data is in a data warehouse, it is stable and remains unchanged.",
      "answer": "non-volatile",
      "choices": [
        "subject-oriented",
        "integrated",
        "time-variant",
        "non-volatile"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a databank that stocks all enterprise data and makes it manageable for reporting.",
      "answer": "data warehouse database",
      "choices": [
        "data warehouse database",
        "material management database",
        "advanced management database",
        "metadata"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This always implemented on the relational database management system (RDBMS) technology like SQL",
      "answer": "data warehouse database",
      "choices": [
        "data warehouse database",
        "technical metadata",
        "business metadata",
        "ETL"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "These tools are used to perform all conversions, summarizations, and changes necessary to transform data into a unified format in the data warehouse.",
      "answer": "Extraction, Transformation, and Loading Tools",
      "choices": [
        "DBSM Tools",
        "Ace Hardware Tools",
        "Query and reporting tool",
        "Extraction, Transformation, and Loading Tools"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about ETL?",
      "answer": "Focuses on the data rather than on the processes that modify the data",
      "choices": [
        "In case of missing data, populating them with defaults",
        "Calculating summaries and derived data",
        "Eliminating unwanted data in operational databases from loading into the data warehouse",
        "Focuses on the data rather than on the processes that modify the data"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about ETL?",
      "answer": "Subjects can be products, customers, departments, regions, etc",
      "choices": [
        "Converting to common data names and definitions",
        "Calculating summaries and derived data",
        "Eliminating unwanted data in operational databases from loading into the data warehouse",
        "Subjects can be products, customers, departments, regions, etc"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is data about data that describes the data warehouse, including the source, transformation, integration, storage, usage, relationships, and history of each data element.",
      "answer": "metadata",
      "choices": [
        "data warehouse database",
        "technical metadata",
        "business metadata",
        "metadata"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is an example of Metadata?",
      "answer": "SNY-JP-0010-15000",
      "choices": [
        "SNY-JP-0010-15000",
        "author_id",
        "Enrolled_Students",
        "int age = 20"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This contains information about the data warehouse, used by designers and administrators.",
      "answer": "technical metadata",
      "choices": [
        "data warehouse database",
        "technical metadata",
        "business metadata",
        "metadata"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This provides details that help end-users easily understand the information stored in the data warehouse.",
      "answer": "business metadata",
      "choices": [
        "data warehouse database",
        "technical metadata",
        "business metadata",
        "metadata"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is TRUE  about Data Warehouse Access Tools?",
      "answer": "Corporate users generally cannot work with databases directly.",
      "choices": [
        "This helps users produce corporate reports for analysis, which can include spreadsheets, calculations, or interactive visuals.",
        "When built-in graphical and analytical tools don't meet an organization's needs, custom reports are created using these tools.",
        "Corporate users generally cannot work with databases directly.",
        "These allow users to analyze the data using elaborate and complex multi-dimensional views."
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the process of finding meaningful correlations, patterns, and trends in large datasets, with data mining tools automating the process.",
      "answer": "Data mining",
      "choices": [
        "Data mining",
        "OLAP tools",
        "Query and reporting tool",
        "Application development tools"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "These allow users to analyze the data using elaborate and complex multi-dimensional views.",
      "answer": "OLAP tools",
      "choices": [
        "Data mining",
        "OLAP tools",
        "Query and reporting tool",
        "Application development tools"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a small, single-subject data warehouse subset that provides decision support for the particular user group.",
      "answer": "data marts",
      "choices": [
        "metadata",
        "data mining",
        "data marts",
        "star schema"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about benefits of a data warehouse?",
      "answer": "Allows organizations to derive valuable business insights from their data to improve decision-making",
      "choices": [
        "This allows business users to quickly access critical data from various sources in one place, saving time by avoiding the need to retrieve data from multiple sources",
        "This provides consistent information on various cross-functional activities and supports ad-hoc reporting and queries",
        "Helps to integrate many sources of data to reduce stress on the production system",
        "Allows organizations to derive valuable business insights from their data to improve decision-making"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about benefits of a data warehouse?",
      "answer": "This optimizes for data retrieval, not for transaction processing",
      "choices": [
        "Helps to reduce total turnaround time for analysis and reporting",
        "Restructuring and integration make it easier for the user to use for reporting and analysis",
        "This stores a large amount of historical data, enabling users to analyze different time periods and trends for future predictions.",
        "This optimizes for data retrieval, not for transaction processing"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Data Sources based on the Data Warehouse Architecture?",
      "answer": "raw data",
      "choices": [
        "operational system",
        "flat files",
        "raw data",
        "operational system"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of Staging Area based on the Data Warehouse Architecture?",
      "answer": "extract transform load",
      "choices": [
        "extract transform load",
        "operational system",
        "analytics",
        "summary data"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Warehouse based on the Data Warehouse Architecture?",
      "answer": "inventory",
      "choices": [
        "inventory",
        "summary data",
        "metadata",
        "raw data"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Data Marts based on the Data Warehouse Architecture?",
      "answer": "metadata",
      "choices": [
        "metadata",
        "purchasing",
        "sales",
        "inventory"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT included in Users based on the Data Warehouse Architecture?",
      "answer": "operational system",
      "choices": [
        "operational system",
        "analytics",
        "reporting",
        "mining"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a data-modeling technique used to map multidimensional decision support data into a relational database.",
      "answer": "star schema",
      "choices": [
        "star schema",
        "facts table",
        "dimension table",
        "single schema"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the two components of star schema?",
      "answer": "facts table and dimension table",
      "choices": [
        "facts table and dimension table",
        "technical metadata and business metadata",
        "query and reporting tool and application development tool",
        "volatile and non-volitle"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are data included in reports that serve as the basis for business decisions, containing measurements or facts and foreign keys to dimension tables.",
      "answer": "facts table",
      "choices": [
        "facts table",
        "dimension table",
        "star schema",
        "single schema"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are attributes that qualify and provide additional information about facts and represent the dimensions of a fact and are linked to the fact table through foreign keys.",
      "answer": "dimension table",
      "choices": [
        "facts table",
        "dimension table",
        "star schema",
        "single schema"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about OLAP?",
      "answer": "It is an operational system that manages the day-to-day",
      "choices": [
        "It is a software tool that is used for data analysis and reporting purposes for business decisions",
        "It is used by business analysts, managers, and executives",
        "This was used for movie recommendations based on watch history in Netflix",
        "It is an operational system that manages the day-to-day"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about OLAP?",
      "answer": "Uses standard queries for data such as inserting, deleting, and updating",
      "choices": [
        "Provides historical data for reporting and planning",
        "Uses complex queries for retrieving a large amount of data",
        "It is a software tool that is used for data analysis and reporting purposes for business decisions",
        "Uses standard queries for data such as inserting, deleting, and updating"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does OLAP stand for?",
      "answer": "Online Analytical Processing",
      "choices": [
        "Online Analytical Processing",
        "Online Analytical Products",
        "Online Analysis Processing",
        "Online Analysis Products"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does OLTP stand for?",
      "answer": "Online Transaction Processing",
      "choices": [
        "Online Transaction Processing",
        "Online Transition Processing",
        "Online Transaction Products",
        "Online Transition Product"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about OLTP?",
      "answer": "Uses complex queries for retrieving a large amount of data",
      "choices": [
        "Uses standard queries for data such as inserting, deleting, and updating",
        "This is used for money withdrawals, transfers, deposits, and inquiries In ATM centers",
        "Uses complex queries for retrieving a large amount of data",
        "Manages day to day operations"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of OLAP allows data to be processed and viewed as part of a multi-dimensional structure?",
      "answer": "Multi-dimensional data analysis techniques",
      "choices": [
        "Multi-dimensional data analysis techniques",
        "Advanced Database support",
        "Easy-to-use end-user interfaces",
        "Online Transaction Processing"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about Advanced Database Support?",
      "answer": "It allows users to navigate data in a way that simplifies and speeds up decision-making or data analysis through easy-to-use graphical interfaces.",
      "choices": [
        "Access to many kinds of DBMSs, flat files, and internal and external data sources",
        "Rapid and consistent query response times",
        "Support for very large databases because the data warehouse could easily and quickly grow to multiple terabytes in size",
        "It allows users to navigate data in a way that simplifies and speeds up decision-making or data analysis through easy-to-use graphical interfaces."
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "It allows users to navigate data in a way that simplifies and speeds up decision-making or data analysis through easy-to-use graphical interfaces.",
      "answer": "Easy-to-use end-user interfaces",
      "choices": [
        "Multi-dimensional data analysis techniques",
        "Advanced Database support",
        "Easy-to-use end-user interfaces",
        "Online Transaction Processing"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP works directly with relational databases?",
      "answer": "ROLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP indicates that fact and dimension tables are stored as relations?",
      "answer": "ROLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP extends its functionality to multi-dimensional database management systems?",
      "answer": "MOLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP is best suited to manage, store, and analyze multi-dimensional data?",
      "answer": "MOLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP uses Star Schema?",
      "answer": "ROLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP uses Data Cubes?",
      "answer": "MOLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP is good with small data sets?",
      "answer": "ROLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP is faster for large data sets?",
      "answer": "MOLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP has unlimited dimensions?",
      "answer": "ROLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of OLAP has limited to preddefined dimensions?",
      "answer": "MOLAP",
      "choices": [
        "ROLAP",
        "MOLAP",
        "OLTP",
        "OTAP"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is an extension of the GROUP BY clause that is used to create subtotals and grand totals for a set of columns.",
      "answer": "ROLLUP operator",
      "choices": [
        "CUBE operator",
        "ROLLUP operator",
        "PIVOT operator",
        "ARITHMETIC operator"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This generates subtotals for all combinations of grouping columns specified in the GROUP BY clause.",
      "answer": "CUBE operator",
      "choices": [
        "CUBE operator",
        "ROLLUP operator",
        "PIVOT operator",
        "ARITHMETIC operator"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This allows you to create a cross-tabulation, enabling you to aggregate results and rotate rows into columns.",
      "answer": "PIVOT operator",
      "choices": [
        "CUBE operator",
        "ROLLUP operator",
        "PIVOT operator",
        "ARITHMETIC operator"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This refers analyzing large amounts of data in a data warehouse or other sources to uncover hidden trends, patterns, and relationships and helps explain the past and predict future outcomes for analysis.",
      "answer": "data mining",
      "choices": [
        "data interaction",
        "data mining",
        "metadata",
        "data nowhere"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "In this step, the goals of the businesses are set, and the important factors that will help in achieving the goal are discovered.",
      "answer": "Business Understanding",
      "choices": [
        "Business Understanding",
        "Data Understanding",
        "Data Preparation",
        "Modeling"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This step will collect the entire data and populate the data in the tool.",
      "answer": "Data Understanding",
      "choices": [
        "Business Understanding",
        "Data Understanding",
        "Data Preparation",
        "Modeling"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This step involves selecting the appropriate data, cleaning, constructing attributes from data, integrating data from multiple databases.",
      "answer": "Data Preparation",
      "choices": [
        "Business Understanding",
        "Data Understanding",
        "Data Preparation",
        "Evaluation"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Selection of the data mining technique such as decision-tree, generate test design for evaluating the selected model, building models from the dataset, and assessing the built model with experts to discuss the result is done in this step",
      "answer": "Modeling",
      "choices": [
        "Deployment",
        "Evaluation",
        "Data Preparation",
        "Modeling"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "This step determines how well the resulting model meets business requirements and is reviewed for any errors or steps that need to be repeated.",
      "answer": "Evaluation",
      "choices": [
        "Deployment",
        "Evaluation",
        "Data Preparation",
        "Modeling"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about Deployment in Data Mining Implementation Process?",
      "answer": "This step will collect the entire data and populate the data in the tool",
      "choices": [
        "A deployment plan is made",
        "The strategy to monitor and maintain the data mining model results to check for its usefulness is formed",
        "Final reports are made, and a review of the whole process is done to check any mistake and see if any step is repeated",
        "This step will collect the entire data and populate the data in the tool"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Data Mining Technique is used to retrieve important and relevant information about data and metadata?",
      "answer": "Classification",
      "choices": [
        "Clustering",
        "Classification",
        "Regression",
        "Prediction"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Data Mining Technique is used to identify similar data, helping to understand the differences and similarities between them?",
      "answer": "Clustering",
      "choices": [
        "Clustering",
        "Classification",
        "Regression",
        "Prediction"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Data Mining Technique is used to identify and analyze the relationship between variables?",
      "answer": "Regression",
      "choices": [
        "Clustering",
        "Association Rules",
        "Regression",
        "Outer Detection"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Data Mining Technique is used to identify associations between two or more items, uncovering hidden patterns in the dataset?",
      "answer": "Association Rules",
      "choices": [
        "Clustering",
        "Association Rules",
        "Regression",
        "Outer Detection"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Data Mining Technique is used to observe data items in the dataset that do not match an expected pattern or expected behavior?",
      "answer": "Outer Detection",
      "choices": [
        "Clustering",
        "Association Rules",
        "Regression",
        "Outer Detection"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Data Mining Technique is used to discover or identify similar patterns or trends in transaction data for a certain period?",
      "answer": "Sequential Patterns",
      "choices": [
        "Sequential Patterns",
        "Association Rules",
        "Regression",
        "Prediction"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Data Mining Technique is used to combine various data mining techniques, such as trends, sequential patterns, clustering, and classification, while analyzing past events or instances in the correct sequence?",
      "answer": "Prediction",
      "choices": [
        "Sequential Patterns",
        "Association Rules",
        "Regression",
        "Prediction"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about benefits of Data Mining?",
      "answer": "Provides historical data for reporting and planning",
      "choices": [
        "Helps with the decision-making process",
        "Helps companies to get knowledge-based information",
        "Facilitates automated prediction of trends and behaviors as well as the automated discovery of hidden patterns",
        "Provides historical data for reporting and planning"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid statement about benefits of Data Mining?",
      "answer": "Support for very large databases because the data warehouse could easily and quickly grow to multiple terabytes in size",
      "choices": [
        "The speedy process which makes it easy for the users to analyze a huge amount of data in less time",
        "Helps companies to get knowledge-based information",
        "Facilitates automated prediction of trends and behaviors as well as the automated discovery of hidden patterns",
        "Support for very large databases because the data warehouse could easily and quickly grow to multiple terabytes in size"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterm"
    }
  ]
}